Guide to the University of Chicago Department of Botany Records 1882-1972
University of Chicago Library
- Series VI: Photographs, circa 1891-1936
  - Subseries 4: 5"x7" Glass Negatives
    - AEP-ILN94, Islands with Salix zones in the Mississippi River two miles north of Savanna, Illinois (Box 55)
    - AEP-ILN95, Wildcat Canyon, Starved Rock State Park, Illinois (Box 55)
    - AEP-ILN96, Horseshoe Canyon, Starved Rock State Park, Illinois (Box 55)
    - AEP-ILN97, Starved Rock and islands in the Illinois River, Starved Rock State Park, Illinois (Box 55)
    - AEP-ILN98, Starved Rock and islands in the Illinois River, Starved Rock State Park, Illinois (Box 55)
    - AEP-ILN99, Aurora Canyon, Starved Rock State Park, Illinois (Box 55)
    - AEP-ILN100, French Canyon, Starved Rock State Park, Illinois (Box 55)
    - AEP-ILN101, Floodplain of the Illinois River near Starved Rock State Park, Illinois (Box 55)
    - AEP-ILN102, Starved Rock State Park, Illinois (Box 55)
    - AEP-ILN103, Starved Rock State Park, Illinois (Box 55)
    - AEP-ILN104, Starved Rock State Park, Illinois (Box 55)
    - AEP-ILN105, Starved Rock State Park, Illinois (Box 55)
    - AEP-ILN106, Starved Rock State Park, Illinois (Box 55)
    - AEP-ILN107, Starved Rock State Park, Illinois (Box 55)
    - AEP-ILN108, Starved Rock State Park, Illinois (Box 55)
    - AEP-ILN109, Starved Rock State Park, Illinois (Box 55)
    - AEP-ILN110, Starved Rock State Park, Illinois (Box 55)
    - AEP-ILN111, Starved Rock State Park, Illinois (Box 55)
    - AEP-ILN112, Starved Rock State Park, Illinois (Box 55)
    - AEP-ILN113, Starved Rock State Park, Illinois (Box 55)
    - AEP-ILN114, A view of Starved Rock, Starved Rock State Park, Illinois (Box 55)
    - AEP-ILN115, A view of Starved Rock, Starved Rock State Park, Illinois (Box 55)
    - AEP-ILN116, Starved Rock State Park, Illinois (Box 55)
    - AEP-ILN117, View of the Illinois River near Starved Rock State Park, Illinois (Box 55)
    - AEP-ILN118, Starved Rock State Park, Illinois (Box 55)
    - AEP-ILN119, Starved Rock State Park, Illinois (Box 55)
    - AEP-ILN120, Starved Rock State Park, Illinois (Box 55)
    - AEP-ILN121, Starved Rock State Park, Illinois (Box 55)
    - AEP-ILN122, Starved Rock State Park, Illinois (Box 55)
    - AEP-ILN123, Starved Rock State Park, Illinois (Box 55)
    - AEP-ILN124, Starved Rock State Park, Illinois (Box 55)
    - AEP-ILN125, A view of Starved Rock and the Illinois River, Starved Rock State Park, Illinois (Box 55)
    - AEP-ILN126, Starved Rock State Park, Illinois (Box 55)
    - AEP-ILN127, Starved Rock State Park, Illinois (Box 55)
    - AEP-ILN128, Starved Rock State Park, Illinois (Box 55)
    - AEP-ILN129, Starved Rock State Park, Illinois (Box 55)
    - AEP-ILN130, Starved Rock State Park, Illinois (Box 55)
    - AEP-ILN131, Starved Rock State Park, Illinois (Box 55)
    - AEP-ILN132, Starved Rock State Park, Illinois (Box 55)
    - AEP-ILN133, An atmometer measuring moisture levels in Starved Rock State Park, Illinois (Box 55)
    - AEP-ILN134, Starved Rock State Park, Illinois (Box 55)
    - AEP-ILN135, Starved Rock State Park, Illinois (Box 55)
    - AEP-ILN136, Starved Rock State Park, Illinois (Box 55)
    - AEP-ILN137, Starved Rock State Park, Illinois (Box 55)
    - AEP-ILN138, Starved Rock State Park, Illinois (Box 55)
    - AEP-ILN139, Starved Rock State Park, Illinois (Box 55)
    - AEP-ILN140, Starved Rock State Park, Illinois (Box 55)
    - AEP-ILN141, Starved Rock State Park, Illinois (Box 55)
    - AEP-ILN142, Starved Rock State Park, Illinois (Box 55)
    - AEP-ILN143, Eagle Cliff, Starved Rock State Park, Illinois (Box 55)
    - AEP-ILN144, Starved Rock State Park, Illinois (Box 55)
    - AEP-ILN145, Starved Rock State Park, Illinois (Box 55)
    - AEP-ILN146, Starved Rock State Park, Illinois (Box 55)
    - AEP-ILN147, Starved Rock State Park, Illinois (Box 55)
    - AEP-ILN148, Starved Rock State Park, Illinois (Box 55)
    - AEP-ILN149, Starved Rock State Park, Illinois (Box 55)
    - AEP-ILN150, Starved Rock State Park, Illinois (Box 55)
    - AEP-ILN151, Starved Rock State Park, Illinois (Box 55)
    - AEP-ILN152, Starved Rock State Park, Illinois (Box 55)
    - AEP-ILN153, Starved Rock State Park, Illinois (Box 55)
    - AEP-ILN154, Starved Rock State Park, Illinois (Box 55)
    - AEP-ILN155, Starved Rock State Park, Illinois (Box 55)
    - AEP-ILN156, Starved Rock State Park, Illinois (Box 55)
    - AEP-ILN157, Starved Rock State Park, Illinois (Box 55)
    - AEP-ILN158, Starved Rock State Park, Illinois (Box 55)
    - Items 1-14: Illinois (Box 56)
    - AEP-ILN159, A view of Starved Rock, Starved Rock State Park, Illinois (Box 56)
    - AEP-ILN160, A view of Starved Rock, Starved Rock State Park, Illinois (Box 56)
    - AEP-ILN161, A view of Starved Rock, Starved Rock State Park, Illinois (Box 56)
    - AEP-ILN162, Starved Rock State Park, Illinois (Box 56)
    - AEP-ILN163, Monument to Pere Jacques Marquette, Summit, Illinois (Box 56)
    - AEP-ILN164, Drainage canal, clay dumps, and a pond, Summit, Illinois (Box 56)
    - AEP-ILN165, Drainage canal, clay dumps, and a pond, Summit, Illinois (Box 56)
    - AEP-ILN166, A University of Chicago Department of Botany Physiographic Ecology class at Willow Springs, Illinois (Box 56)
    - AEP-ILN167, An eroding bank at Thorn Creek with an Oak forest on upland, Thornton, Illinois (Box 56)
    - AEP-ILN170, Eroding clay cliff, Thorn Creek, Thornton, Illinois (Box 56)
    - AEP-ILN171, Juniperus horizontalis, Waukegan, Illinois (Box 56)
    - AEP-ILN172, Verbascum thapsus, Chicago, Illinois (Box 56)
    - AEP-ILN173, Forest and prairie tension line, Washington Heights, Illinois (Box 56)
    - Items 15-70: Indiana (Box 56)
    - AEP-INN1, Decodon verticillatus advancing on a Water Lily association, Bailly Town, Indiana (Box 56)
    - AEP-INN16, A blowout with Juniperus and Pinus, Dune Park, Chesterton, Indiana (Box 56)
    - AEP-INN17, A graveyard of Pine, Dune Park, between Furnessville and Chesterton, Indiana (Box 56)
    - AEP-INN18, A forest graveyard of Pinus strobus, Dune Park, Chesterton, Indiana (Box 56)
    - AEP-INN19, Pinus strobus and Pinus banksiana on an old erosional dune face, Dune Park, Chesterton, Indiana (Box 56)
    - AEP-INN20, Embryo dunes with Great Lakes Sand Cherry, Dune Park, Chesterton, Indiana (Box 56)
    - AEP-INN21, A dune advancing upon a forest, Chesterton, Indiana (Box 56)
    - AEP-INN22, Dune moving over a forest, Dune Park, Chesterton, Indiana (Box 56)
    - AEP-INN23, Dunes with Salix and Vitis between Tremont and Chesterton, Indiana (Box 56)
    - AEP-INN24, A beach and foredunes, Chesterton, Indiana (Box 56)
    - AEP-INN25, A dune landscape, Chesterton, Indiana (Box 56)
    - AEP-INN36, The Crater, a rejuvenated dune, Dune Park, Indiana (Box 56)
    - AEP-INN37, Basswood and Calamagrostis at the top of a rejuvenated dune, Dune Park, Indiana (Box 56)
    - AEP-INN41, Vitis cordifolia, Prunus virginiana, and Corispermum growing on dunes which encroach on a Fraxinus and Tilia forest, Dune Park, Indiana (Box 56)
    - AEP-INN47, Wind sculpture of damp sand, Dune Park, Indiana (Box 56)
    - AEP-INN48, Pine and Cottonwood dunes near the "new crater," Dune Park, Indiana (Box 56)
    - AEP-INN49, Pine and Cottonwood dunes, Dune Park, Indiana (Box 56)
    - AEP-INN50, The New Crater, Dune Park, Indiana (Box 56)
    - AEP-INN51, The New Crater, Dune Park, Indiana (Box 56)
    - AEP-INN52, A steam shovel removing a dune, Dune Park, Indiana (Box 56)
    - AEP-INN53, The Crater, Dune Park, Indiana (Box 56)
    - AEP-INN54, The Crater, Dune Park, Indiana (Box 56)
    - AEP-INN55, The Crater, Dune Park, Indiana (Box 56)
    - AEP-INN56, The Crater, Dune Park, Indiana (Box 56)
    - AEP-INN57, Smilacina stellata on the dunes, Dune Park, Indiana (Box 56)
    - AEP-INN58, Gentiana crinita, Dune Park, Indiana (Box 56)
    - AEP-INN59, Ceanothus americanus, Dune Park, Indiana (Box 56)
    - AEP-INN60, An advancing dune complex, Dune Park, Indiana (Box 56)
    - AEP-INN61, A mesophytic forest of Ash, Tuliptree, Basswood, Elm, and Black Willow overcome by an advancing dune, Dune Park, Indiana (Box 56)
    - AEP-INN62, A sandy flat, Dune Park, Indiana (Box 56)
    - AEP-INN63, An advance of dunes inland, Dune Park, Wilson, Indiana (Box 56)
    - AEP-INN64, An advancing dune complex, Dune Park, Wilson, Indiana (Box 56)
    - AEP-INN65, A dune landscape with Pine, Dune Park, Wilson, Indiana (Box 56)
    - AEP-INN66, Dunes advancing over Pine and Willow, Dune Park, Wilson, Indiana (Box 56)
    - AEP-INN67, Forested dunes, Dune Park, Wilson, Indiana (Box 56)
    - AEP-INN68, Wind sweep around the Crater peak, Dune Park, Wilson, Indiana (Box 56)
    - AEP-INN69, A forest graveyard, Dune Park, Wilson, Indiana (Box 56)
    - AEP-INN70, A dune landscape with Pine, Dune Park, Wilson, Indiana (Box 56)
    - AEP-INN71, A dune remnant, Dune Park, Wilson, Indiana (Box 56)
    - AEP-INN72, An advance of dunes over a swamp, Dune Park, Wilson, Indiana (Box 56)
    - AEP-INN73, A lone Cottonwood, Dune Park, Wilson, Indiana (Box 56)
    - AEP-INN74, Passing of Basswood on the dunes, Dune Park, Wilson, Indiana (Box 56)
    - AEP-INN75, A dune landscape, Dune Park, Wilson, Indiana (Box 56)
    - AEP-INN76, A recent line of Cottonwood with embryo dunes in the foreground and older beach edges of Cottonwood in the background, Dune Park, Indiana (Box 56)
    - AEP-INN77, A dune landscape, Dune Park, Wilson, Indiana (Box 56)
    - AEP-INN78, A dune landscape, Dune Park, Wilson, Indiana (Box 56)
    - AEP-INN79, A dune landscape, Dune Park, Wilson, Indiana (Box 56)
    - AEP-INN80, Oak in a dune landscape, Dune Park, Indiana (Box 56)
    - AEP-INN81, The mutual advance of opposing dunes, Dune Park, Wilson, Indiana (Box 56)
    - AEP-INN82, Dunes advancing over a marsh, Dune Park, Wilson, Indiana (Box 56)
    - AEP-INN83, A dune landscape with Pine and Virginia Creeper, Dune Park, Wilson, Indiana (Box 56)
    - AEP-INN84, The Crater in winter, Dune Park, Wilson, Indiana (Box 56)
    - AEP-INN85, Erosion remnants on the dunes held by Vitis, Dune Park, Wilson, Indiana (Box 56)
    - AEP-INN86, A general view of the dunes, Dune Park, Indiana (Box 56)
    - Items 1-70: Indiana (Box 57)
    - AEP-INN87, An open dune landscape, Dune Park, Wilson, Indiana (Box 57)
    - AEP-INN88, Cottonwood roots exposed by windswept sand, Dune Park, Wilson, Indiana (Box 57)
    - AEP-INN89, The lee slope of a dune advancing over a Pine and Oak forest, Dune Park, Wilson, Indiana (Box 57)
    - AEP-INN90, A dune advancing over a Pine forest, Dune Park, Wilson, Indiana (Box 57)
    - AEP-INN91, A dune advancing over a marsh, Dune Park, Wilson, Indiana (Box 57)
    - AEP-INN92, A dune advancing over a marsh, Dune Park, Wilson, Indiana (Box 57)
    - AEP-INN93, A dune advancing over Pinus strobus, between Furnessville and Dune Park, Indiana (Box 57)
    - AEP-INN94, A dune encroaching on a forest, Dune Park, Wilson, Indiana (Box 57)
    - AEP-INN95, Dune park, Wilson, Indiana (Box 57)
    - AEP-INN96, A dune encroaching on a forest, Dune Park, Wilson, Indiana (Box 57)
    - AEP-INN97, A lone Cottonwood on a dune, Dune Park, Wilson, Indiana (Box 57)
    - AEP-INN98, Oak in a dune landscape, Dune Park, Wilson, Indiana (Box 57)
    - AEP-INN99, A shoreline in the region east of Dune Park, Wilson, Indiana (Box 57)
    - AEP-INN100, Established dunes forested with Pine and Oak, Porter County, Indiana (Box 57)
    - AEP-INN101, Sand drifting over Calamovilfa longifolia and Prunus pumila, Dune Park, Indiana (Box 57)
    - AEP-INN102, A University of Chicago Department of Botany Field Ecology class on a dune advancing over a mesophytic forest, Furnessville, Indiana (Box 57)
    - AEP-INN103, Members of the International Phytogeographic Excursion in America, Miller, Indiana (Box 57)
    - AEP-INN104, Members of the International Phytogeographic Excursion in America on the dunes, Miller, Indiana (Box 57)
    - AEP-INN105, Sand dunes advancing over a mesophytic forest, Furnessville, Indiana (Box 57)
    - AEP-INN106, Dunes advancing over trees and into a lake, Furnessville, Indiana (Box 57)
    - AEP-INN109, Lupinus perennis, Mineral Springs, Indiana (Box 57)
    - AEP-INN110, Cypripedium acaule, Mineral Springs, Indiana (Box 57)
    - AEP-INN111, Cypripedium parviflorum, Mineral Springs, Indiana (Box 57)
    - AEP-INN112, Decodon verticillatus, Mineral Springs, Indiana (Box 57)
    - AEP-INN113, Pyrus arbutifolia, Mineral Springs, Indiana (Box 57)
    - AEP-INN114, Opuntia rafinesquei, Mineral Springs, Indiana (Box 57)
    - AEP-INN115, Pinus banksiana and Juniperus communis on the dunes, Dune Park, Wilson, Indiana (Box 57)
    - AEP-INN123, Vegetation on the dunes, Dune Park, Indiana (Box 57)
    - AEP-INN124, The front of a moving dune, Dune Park, Indiana (Box 57)
    - AEP-INN125, A dune landscape, Indiana (Box 57)
    - AEP-INN126, A high moving dune north of a Pinus thicket with Andropogon scoparius in the foreground, Miller, Indiana (Box 57)
    - AEP-INN127, Ophioglossum vulgatum, Gary, Indiana (Box 57)
    - AEP-INN128, Decodon, Mill Creek, Indiana (Box 57)
    - AEP-INN129, Decodon, Mill Creek, Indiana (Box 57)
    - AEP-INN130, Larix laricina swamp, Mill Creek, Indiana (Box 57)
    - AEP-INN131, Larix laricina swamp, Mill Creek, Indiana (Box 57)
    - AEP-INN132, Celtis occidentalis var. pumila, Miller, Indiana (Box 57)
    - AEP-INN133, Cornus stolonifera and Quercus velutina on an eroding dune, Miller, Indiana (Box 57)
    - AEP-INN134, Pontederia cordata, Miller, Indiana (Box 57)
    - AEP-INN135, Pontederia cordata, Miller, Indiana (Box 57)
    - AEP-INN136, A sand dune advancing over Pinus banksiana, Miller, Indiana (Box 57)
    - AEP-INN137, A forest with Pinus banksiana, Pinus strobus, and Juniperus communis, Miller, Indiana (Box 57)
    - AEP-INN138, A foredune with Great Lakes Sand Cherry, Miller, Indiana (Box 57)
    - AEP-INN139, Prunus pumila on a foredune, Miller, Indiana (Box 57)
    - AEP-INN140, Prunus pumila holding an eroded dune, Miller, Indiana (Box 57)
    - AEP-INN141, Prunus pumila holding a dune remnant, Miller, Indiana (Box 57)
    - AEP-INN142, Looking west at a low foredune on the beach with Prunus pumila and an early panne in front of eroding Populus dunes, Miller, Indiana (Box 57)
    - AEP-INN143, A beach with small foredune, a panne with Prunus pumila and Populus deltoides seedling, Miller, Indiana (Box 57)
    - AEP-INN145, Prunus virginiana on an eroding dune, a view toward the lake, Miller, Indiana (Box 57)
    - AEP-INN146, Prunus virginiana on an eroding dune with slumps of Juniperus, Long Lake, Miller, Indiana (Box 57)
    - AEP-INN147, Prunus virginiana on an eroding dune, Long Lake, Miller, Indiana (Box 57)
    - AEP-INN148, Oak and Pine on opposite dune faces, Miller, Indiana (Box 57)
    - AEP-INN149, Swamp with Arrowhead bordered by Pine possibly north of the Grand Calumet River, Miller, Indiana (Box 57)
    - AEP-INN150, The exit of Water Lily in a swamp, Miller, Indiana (Box 57)
    - AEP-INN151, Dune remnants with grapevine smothering Pine, Miller, Indiana (Box 57)
    - AEP-INN152, A swamp with Typha and thick forest cover probably on the north side of the Grand Calumet River, Miller, Indiana (Box 57)
    - AEP-INN153, Wind erosion uncovering adventitious roots of Populus deltoides, Miller, Indiana (Box 57)
    - AEP-INN154, Miller, Indiana (Box 57)
    - AEP-INN155, An eroding dune remnant with Cottonwood west of the road, Miller, Indiana (Box 57)
    - AEP-INN156, An eroding dune remnant with Cottonwood, Miller, Indiana (Box 57)
    - AEP-INN157, An embryonic Cottonwood dune ridge, Miller, Indiana (Box 57)
    - AEP-INN158, Miller, Indiana (Box 57)
    - AEP-INN162, One to six year old Populus deltoides seedling in panne and a tuft of Juncus balticus var. littoralis suggesting defoliation, Miller, Indiana (Box 57)
    - AEP-INN163, A panne with abundant seedling of Populus deltoides ranging from three to ten years old, Miller, Indiana (Box 57)
    - AEP-INN164, A large Cottonwood dune near the road, Miller, Indiana (Box 57)
    - AEP-INN165, A close view of a foredune, a panne, and Cottonwood dunes, Miller, Indiana (Box 57)
    - AEP-INN166, A panne with seedling of Populus deltoides, Miller, Indiana (Box 57)
    - AEP-INN167, Miller, Indiana (Box 57)
    - AEP-INN168, Populus deltoides seedling on a panne near the road and bridge, Miller, Indiana (Box 57)
    - Items 1-31: Indiana (Box 58)
    - AEP-INN169, Populus deltoides on a panne and on a dune just west of Millers road, Miller, Indiana (Box 58)
    - AEP-INN170, Looking southwest landward along Millers road at a Populus dune, Miller, Indiana (Box 58)
    - AEP-INN171, A panne with Cottonwood seedling, Miller, Indiana (Box 58)
    - AEP-INN174, A dune advancing into the Grand Calumet River, Miller, Indiana (Box 58)
    - AEP-INN175, A dune advancing into the Grand Calumet River at the bridge, Miller, Indiana (Box 58)
    - AEP-INN176, Looking west from the beach, a small foredune and bare panne, Miller, Indiana (Box 58)
    - AEP-INN177, The east side of Millers road, Miller, Indiana (Box 58)
    - AEP-INN178, A portion of a deserted channel along the Grand Calumet River west of the bridge at the lakeshore on Millers Road, Miller, Indiana (Box 58)
    - AEP-INN179, A deserted channel of the Grand Calumet River with an embryo swamp and a forest of Pinus banksiana, Miller, Indiana (Box 58)
    - AEP-INN180, The encroachment of sand on the Grand Calumet River, Miller, Indiana (Box 58)
    - AEP-INN181, Dunes moving into the Grand Calumet River, Miller, Indiana (Box 58)
    - AEP-INN182, The shoreline of Lake Michigan near the Indiana and Michigan border, Indiana (Box 58)
    - AEP-INN189, A forest of Beech and Maple, Otis, Indiana (Box 58)
    - AEP-INN190, A forest of Beech and Maple with Basswood seedling, Otis, Indiana (Box 58)
    - AEP-INN193, Indiana (Box 58)
    - AEP-INN194, Indiana (Box 58)
    - AEP-INN197, Prunus virginiana on an eroding dune, Long Lake, Miller, Indiana (Box 58)
    - Items 32-70: Michigan (Box 58)
    - AEP-MIN1, Abies balsamea, Pinus resinosa, and Picea on dunes, Bay View, Michigan (Box 58)
    - AEP-MIN2, Close-up of an Acer pensylvanicum in a Tsuga and Fagus forest on low 100 foot fixed dunes, Bay View, Michigan (Box 58)
    - AEP-MIN3, Acer pensylvanicum in a mesophytic forest, Bay View, Michigan (Box 58)
    - AEP-MIN4, Acer spicatum in a mesophytic forest, Bay View, Michigan (Box 58)
    - AEP-MIN5, Amelanchier spicata and Myrica aspleniifolia on sand in the Pine Barrens, Bay View, Michigan (Box 58)
    - AEP-MIN6, Beech, Maple, and Hemlock Forest, Bay View, Michigan (Box 58)
    - AEP-MIN7, Larix laricina and grasses at the edge of a swamp in the Pine Barrens, Bay View, Michigan (Box 58)
    - AEP-MIN8, Myrica aspleniifolia on outwashed sand, Bay View, Michigan (Box 58)
    - AEP-MIN9, Pinus banksiana in the Pine Barrens, Bay View, Michigan (Box 58)
    - AEP-MIN10, Pinus banksiana in the Pine Barrens, Bay View, Michigan (Box 58)
    - AEP-MIN11, Pinus banksiana, Quercus rubra, and Myrica aspleniifolia in the Pine Barrens, Bay View, Michigan (Box 58)
    - AEP-MIN12, Pinus banksiana with Danthonia spicata on outwashed sand, Bay View, Michigan (Box 58)
    - AEP-MIN13, Pinus resinosa, Juniperus communis, Prunus pumila, and Arctostaphylos at the outer margin of dunes, Bay View, Michigan (Box 58)
    - AEP-MIN14, Dune forest with Tsuga, Fagus, Pinus strobus, and young Acer and Betula, Bay View, Michigan (Box 58)
    - AEP-MIN15, Zigadenus chlorantha on a dune, Bay View, Michigan (Box 58)
    - AEP-MIN16, A 200 foot forested dune with conifers, Bay View, Michigan (Box 58)
    - AEP-MIN17, Forested dunes on dune ridges, Bay View, Michigan (Box 58)
    - AEP-MIN18, University of Chicago Department of Botany Field Ecology class, Bay View, Michigan (Box 58)
    - AEP-MIN19, Bay View, Michigan (Box 58)
    - AEP-MIN20, Bay View, Michigan (Box 58)
    - AEP-MIN21, University of Chicago Department of Botany Field Ecology class, Bay View, Michigan (Box 58)
    - AEP-MIN38, Acer pensylvanicum on open dunes that were once forested, Charlevoix, Michigan (Box 58)
    - AEP-MIN39, Populus balsamifera, Thuja, and Abies on a dune, Charlevoix, Michigan (Box 58)
    - AEP-MIN40, Adventitious roots from Thuja occidentalis trunks on the dunes, Charlevoix, Michigan (Box 58)
    - AEP-MIN41, Adventitious roots from Thuja trunks on the dunes, Charlevoix, Michigan (Box 58)
    - AEP-MIN42, Adventitious roots from Thuja trunks on the dunes, Charlevoix, Michigan (Box 58)
    - AEP-MIN43, Adventitious roots from buried Thuja trunks on the dunes, Charlevoix, Michigan (Box 58)
    - AEP-MIN44, Abies balsamea with Juniperus on dunes, Frankfort, Michigan (Box 58)
    - AEP-MIN45, Dune depression with Abies balsamea, Pinus strobus, Juniperus communis, Juniperus horizontalis, and Arctostaphylos, Frankfort, Michigan (Box 58)
    - AEP-MIN46, Clump of Abies balsamea on dunes, Frankfort, Michigan (Box 58)
    - AEP-MIN47, Acer, Betula lutea, and Taxus on fixed dunes, Frankfort, Michigan (Box 58)
    - AEP-MIN48, Acer and Tsuga forest on top of fixed dunes, Frankfort, Michigan (Box 58)
    - AEP-MIN49, Acer saccharum and Tsuga canadensis on top of fixed dunes, Frankfort, Michigan (Box 58)
    - AEP-MIN50, Betula papyrifera being covered by an advancing dune to the depth of twenty feet, Frankfort, Michigan (Box 58)
    - AEP-MIN51, Betula lutea with Taxus in a mesophytic forest on the dunes, Frankfort, Michigan (Box 58)
    - AEP-MIN52, Betula lutea on dunes, Frankfort, Michigan (Box 58)
    - Items 1-70: Michigan (Box 59)
    - AEP-MIN54, Fagus grandifolia and Tsuga canadensis with seedling of both on fixed dunes, Frankfort, Michigan (Box 59)
    - AEP-MIN55, Beech and Hemlock seedling on fixed dunes, Frankfort, Michigan (Box 59)
    - AEP-MIN56, Forest on fixed dunes with Fagus seedling and Tsuga, Frankfort, Michigan (Box 59)
    - AEP-MIN57, Beech and Hemlock forest on fixed dunes, Frankfort, Michigan (Box 59)
    - AEP-MIN58, Beech and Maple forest on fixed dunes along a road, Frankfort, Michigan (Box 59)
    - AEP-MIN59, Beech, Maple, and Hemlock forest near the top of fixed dunes, Frankfort, Michigan (Box 59)
    - AEP-MIN60, Beech and Hemlock forest with Yew on dunes, Frankfort, Michigan (Box 59)
    - AEP-MIN61, Fagus and Acer with seedling near the crest of fixed dunes, Frankfort, Michigan (Box 59)
    - AEP-MIN62, Juniperus communis, Abies balsamea, Thuja occidentalis, and Betula papyrifera in a depression, Frankfort, Michigan (Box 59)
    - AEP-MIN63, C. E. Spicer standing in front of a Juniperus communis on a dune, Frankfort, Michigan (Box 59)
    - AEP-MIN66, Pinus strobus, Pinus resinosa, Pinus banksiana, Abies balsamea, and Thuja on dunes, Frankfort, Michigan (Box 59)
    - AEP-MIN67, Populus balsamifera, Frankfort, Michigan (Box 59)
    - AEP-MIN68, Prunus pensylvanica, Pteris, and Rhus typhina on a fixed dune, Frankfort, Michigan (Box 59)
    - AEP-MIN69, Quercus borealis var. maxima with Acer saccharum, Frankfort, Michigan (Box 59)
    - AEP-MIN71, Taxus, Thuja, and Acer on fixed dunes, Frankfort, Michigan (Box 59)
    - AEP-MIN72, Dune advancing over Thuja occidentalis and Abies balsamea with Ammophila on its lee side, Frankfort, Michigan (Box 59)
    - AEP-MIN73, Dune with Ammophila advancing over a Thuja and Abies forest, Frankfort, Michigan (Box 59)
    - AEP-MIN74, Forest of Thuja and Abies on a dune, Frankfort, Michigan (Box 59)
    - AEP-MIN75, Tsuga canadensis seedling on a log in a dune forest, Frankfort, Michigan (Box 59)
    - AEP-MIN76, Tsuga growing on fixed dunes along a road, Frankfort, Michigan (Box 59)
    - AEP-MIN77, Tsuga, Fagus, and Taxus on fixed dunes, Frankfort, Michigan (Box 59)
    - AEP-MIN78, Forest of Tsuga, Acer, and Fagus near the crest of dunes, Frankfort, Michigan (Box 59)